[
    {
        "Paragraph": "HNB Finance subsidiary Hatton National Bank PLC unblemished record almost two decades leader finance industry diverse portfolio financial products services .",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB Finance",
                "ORG",
                0,
                11
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "Mehewara fund series ongoing CSR projects our customers need . fund financial contribution our dedicated employees organisation .",
        "entities": []
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "News Updates our latest news updates . HNB FINANCE partners Kiya.ai January , HNB FINANCE presence branch Mullaitivu January , HNB FINANCE International Women s Day March , HNB Finance young minds Yalu Daskam Art Workshop Wijeyawardana Vidyalaya February , HNB FINANCE partners Kiya.ai January , HNB FINANCE presence branch Mullaitivu January , HNB FINANCE International Women s Day March , HNB Finance young minds Yalu Daskam Art Workshop Wijeyawardana Vidyalaya February , prev next",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB FINANCE",
                "ORG",
                39,
                50
            ],
            [
                "Yalu Daskam Art Workshop Wijeyawardana Vidyalaya February",
                "PRODUCT",
                197,
                254
            ],
            [
                "HNB FINANCE",
                "ORG",
                257,
                268
            ],
            [
                "Yalu Daskam Art Workshop Wijeyawardana Vidyalaya February",
                "PRODUCT",
                415,
                472
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "Us financial institution passionate team customer centric , well diversified products services responsible sustainable way . Customers Employees Branches",
        "entities": []
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "HNB FINANCE International Women s Day March",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB FINANCE International",
                "PRODUCT",
                0,
                25
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "HNB FINANCE been immense strength our lives",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB FINANCE",
                "ORG",
                0,
                11
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "HNB Finance PLC Strength Strength HNB Finance subsidiary Hatton National Bank PLC unblemished record almost two decades leader finance industry diverse portfolio financial products services .",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB Finance PLC",
                "ORG",
                0,
                15
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "Products your future products growth",
        "entities": []
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "Customers Employees Branches",
        "entities": []
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "Success Stories Our keen focus entrepreneurs across country us SME SSE communities their full potential .",
        "entities": [
            [
                "SME",
                "ORG",
                63,
                66
            ],
            [
                "SSE",
                "ORG",
                67,
                70
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "I benefit money business while",
        "entities": []
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "Sri Lanka s financial service provider HNB Finance water purification system Mohoththuwarama",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Sri Lanka",
                "GPE",
                0,
                9
            ],
            [
                "HNB Finance",
                "ORG",
                39,
                50
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "HNB FINANCE International Women s Day",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB FINANCE International",
                "PRODUCT",
                0,
                25
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "HNB Finance young minds Yalu Daskam Art Workshop Wijeyawardana Vidyalaya February",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB Finance",
                "ORG",
                0,
                11
            ],
            [
                "Yalu Daskam Art Workshop Wijeyawardana Vidyalaya February",
                "PRODUCT",
                24,
                81
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "HNB Finance oasis Mohoththuwarama Primary School",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB Finance",
                "ORG",
                0,
                11
            ],
            [
                "Mohoththuwarama Primary School",
                "PRODUCT",
                18,
                48
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "our latest news updates .",
        "entities": []
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "Mehewara CSR Projects",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Mehewara CSR Projects",
                "SERVICE",
                0,
                21
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "HNB Finance subsidiary Hatton National Bank PLC unblemished record almost two decades leader finance industry diverse portfolio financial products services .",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB Finance",
                "ORG",
                0,
                11
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "HNB Finance PLC",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB Finance PLC",
                "ORG",
                0,
                15
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "Mehewara CSR Projects Mehewara fund series ongoing CSR projects our customers need . fund financial contribution our dedicated employees organisation . HNB Finance oasis Mohoththuwarama Primary School Sri Lanka s financial service provider HNB Finance water purification system Mohoththuwarama",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Mehewara CSR Projects Mehewara",
                "SERVICE",
                0,
                30
            ],
            [
                "HNB Finance",
                "ORG",
                152,
                163
            ],
            [
                "Mohoththuwarama Primary School",
                "PRODUCT",
                170,
                200
            ],
            [
                "HNB Finance",
                "ORG",
                240,
                251
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "HNB FINANCE been immense strength our lives HNB FINANCE been our financial partner over years now . Therefore , we have been able business",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB FINANCE",
                "ORG",
                0,
                11
            ],
            [
                "HNB",
                "ORG",
                44,
                47
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "Sri Lanka s financial service provider HNB Finance water purification system Mohoththuwarama",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Sri Lanka",
                "GPE",
                0,
                9
            ],
            [
                "HNB Finance",
                "ORG",
                39,
                50
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "HNB FINANCE International Women s Day",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB FINANCE International",
                "PRODUCT",
                0,
                25
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "Strength Born Strength",
        "entities": []
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "our latest news updates .",
        "entities": []
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "HNB FINANCE partners Kiya.ai January , HNB FINANCE presence branch Mullaitivu January , HNB FINANCE International Women s Day March , HNB Finance young minds Yalu Daskam Art Workshop Wijeyawardana Vidyalaya February , HNB FINANCE partners Kiya.ai January , HNB FINANCE presence branch Mullaitivu January , HNB FINANCE International Women s Day March , HNB Finance young minds Yalu Daskam Art Workshop Wijeyawardana Vidyalaya February , prev next",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB FINANCE",
                "ORG",
                0,
                11
            ],
            [
                "Yalu Daskam Art Workshop Wijeyawardana Vidyalaya February",
                "PRODUCT",
                158,
                215
            ],
            [
                "HNB FINANCE",
                "ORG",
                218,
                229
            ],
            [
                "Yalu Daskam",
                "PRODUCT",
                376,
                387
            ],
            [
                "Art Workshop Wijeyawardana Vidyalaya February",
                "PRODUCT",
                388,
                433
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "HNB FINANCE presence branch Mullaitivu January",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB FINANCE",
                "ORG",
                0,
                11
            ],
            [
                "Mullaitivu January",
                "SERVICE",
                28,
                46
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "This website cookies best experience our website .",
        "entities": []
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "News Updates our latest news updates .",
        "entities": []
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "HNB Finance young minds Yalu Daskam Art Workshop Wijeyawardana Vidyalaya",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB Finance",
                "ORG",
                0,
                11
            ],
            [
                "Yalu Daskam Art Workshop Wijeyawardana Vidyalaya",
                "PRODUCT",
                24,
                72
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "Strength Born Strength",
        "entities": []
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "Success Stories Our keen focus entrepreneurs across country us SME SSE communities their full potential . HNB FINANCE been immense strength our lives HNB FINANCE been our financial partner over years now . Therefore , we have been able business so . I benefit money business while I able loan without any guarantors through Swashakthi Savings , I able easily money I .",
        "entities": [
            [
                "SME",
                "ORG",
                63,
                66
            ],
            [
                "SSE",
                "ORG",
                67,
                70
            ],
            [
                "HNB",
                "ORG",
                106,
                109
            ],
            [
                "HNB",
                "ORG",
                150,
                153
            ],
            [
                "Swashakthi Savings",
                "PRODUCT",
                324,
                342
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "HNB Finance oasis Mohoththuwarama Primary School Sri Lanka s financial service provider HNB Finance water purification system Mohoththuwarama",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB Finance",
                "ORG",
                0,
                11
            ],
            [
                "Mohoththuwarama Primary School",
                "PRODUCT",
                18,
                48
            ],
            [
                "HNB Finance",
                "ORG",
                88,
                99
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "Mehewara CSR Projects Mehewara fund series ongoing CSR projects our customers need . fund financial contribution our dedicated employees organisation . HNB Finance oasis Mohoththuwarama Primary School Sri Lanka s financial service provider HNB Finance water purification system Mohoththuwarama",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Mehewara CSR Projects Mehewara",
                "SERVICE",
                0,
                30
            ],
            [
                "HNB Finance",
                "ORG",
                152,
                163
            ],
            [
                "Mohoththuwarama Primary School",
                "PRODUCT",
                170,
                200
            ],
            [
                "HNB Finance",
                "ORG",
                240,
                251
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "Services Convenience Flexibility HNB Finance PLC Strength Strength HNB Finance subsidiary Hatton National Bank PLC unblemished record almost two decades leader finance industry diverse portfolio financial products services . Products your future products growth Success Stories Our keen focus entrepreneurs across country us SME SSE communities their full potential . HNB FINANCE been immense strength our lives HNB FINANCE been our financial partner over years now . Therefore , we have been able business so . I benefit money business while I able loan without any guarantors through Swashakthi Savings , I able easily money I . Us financial institution passionate team customer centric , well diversified products services responsible sustainable way . Customers Employees Branches Mehewara CSR Projects Mehewara fund series ongoing CSR projects our customers need . fund financial contribution our dedicated employees organisation . HNB Finance oasis Mohoththuwarama Primary School Sri Lanka s financial service provider HNB Finance water purification system Mohoththuwarama Pri . News Updates our latest news updates . HNB FINANCE partners Kiya.ai January , HNB FINANCE presence branch Mullaitivu January , HNB FINANCE International Women s Day March , HNB Finance young minds Yalu Daskam Art Workshop Wijeyawardana Vidyalaya February , HNB FINANCE partners Kiya.ai January , HNB FINANCE presence branch Mullaitivu January , HNB FINANCE International Women s Day March , HNB Finance young minds Yalu Daskam Art Workshop Wijeyawardana Vidyalaya February , prev next Great Place TAGS Awards",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB Finance PLC",
                "ORG",
                33,
                48
            ],
            [
                "SME",
                "ORG",
                325,
                328
            ],
            [
                "SSE",
                "ORG",
                329,
                332
            ],
            [
                "HNB",
                "ORG",
                368,
                371
            ],
            [
                "HNB",
                "ORG",
                412,
                415
            ],
            [
                "Swashakthi Savings",
                "PRODUCT",
                586,
                604
            ],
            [
                "HNB Finance",
                "ORG",
                937,
                948
            ],
            [
                "Mohoththuwarama Primary School",
                "PRODUCT",
                955,
                985
            ],
            [
                "HNB Finance",
                "ORG",
                1025,
                1036
            ],
            [
                "HNB FINANCE",
                "ORG",
                1124,
                1135
            ],
            [
                "Yalu Daskam Art Workshop Wijeyawardana Vidyalaya February",
                "PRODUCT",
                1282,
                1339
            ],
            [
                "HNB FINANCE",
                "ORG",
                1342,
                1353
            ],
            [
                "Yalu Daskam Art Workshop Wijeyawardana Vidyalaya February",
                "PRODUCT",
                1500,
                1557
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "HNB Finance oasis Mohoththuwarama Primary School Sri Lanka s financial service provider HNB Finance water purification system Mohoththuwarama",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB Finance",
                "ORG",
                0,
                11
            ],
            [
                "Mohoththuwarama Primary School",
                "PRODUCT",
                18,
                48
            ],
            [
                "HNB Finance",
                "ORG",
                88,
                99
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "financial institution passionate team customer centric , well diversified products services responsible sustainable",
        "entities": []
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "Services Convenience Flexibility",
        "entities": []
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "your future products growth",
        "entities": []
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "HNB FINANCE been our financial partner over years now . Therefore , we have been able business",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB FINANCE",
                "ORG",
                0,
                11
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "Us financial institution passionate team customer centric , well diversified products services responsible sustainable",
        "entities": []
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "I benefit money business while I able loan without any guarantors through Swashakthi Savings , I able easily money I .",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Swashakthi Savings",
                "PRODUCT",
                43,
                61
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "HNB FINANCE partners Kiya.ai January",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB FINANCE",
                "ORG",
                0,
                11
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "HNB FINANCE partners Kiya.ai January , HNB FINANCE presence branch Mullaitivu January , HNB FINANCE International Women s Day March , HNB Finance young minds Yalu Daskam Art Workshop Wijeyawardana Vidyalaya February , HNB FINANCE partners Kiya.ai January , HNB FINANCE presence branch Mullaitivu January , HNB FINANCE International Women s Day March , HNB Finance young minds Yalu Daskam Art Workshop Wijeyawardana Vidyalaya February , prev next",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB FINANCE",
                "ORG",
                0,
                11
            ],
            [
                "Yalu Daskam Art Workshop Wijeyawardana Vidyalaya February",
                "PRODUCT",
                158,
                215
            ],
            [
                "HNB FINANCE",
                "ORG",
                218,
                229
            ],
            [
                "Yalu Daskam",
                "PRODUCT",
                376,
                387
            ],
            [
                "Art Workshop Wijeyawardana Vidyalaya February",
                "PRODUCT",
                388,
                433
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "Mehewara fund series ongoing CSR projects our customers need . fund financial contribution our dedicated employees organisation .",
        "entities": []
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "HNB FINANCE been immense strength our lives HNB FINANCE been our financial partner over years now . Therefore , we have been able business so . I benefit money business while I able loan without any guarantors through Swashakthi Savings , I able easily money I .",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB FINANCE",
                "ORG",
                0,
                11
            ],
            [
                "HNB",
                "ORG",
                44,
                47
            ],
            [
                "Swashakthi Savings",
                "PRODUCT",
                218,
                236
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "HNB FINANCE International Women s Day March",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB FINANCE International",
                "PRODUCT",
                0,
                25
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "Success Stories Our keen focus entrepreneurs across country us SME SSE communities their full potential . HNB FINANCE been immense strength our lives HNB FINANCE been our financial partner over years now . Therefore , we have been able business so . I benefit money business while I able loan without any guarantors through Swashakthi Savings , I able easily money I .",
        "entities": [
            [
                "SME",
                "ORG",
                63,
                66
            ],
            [
                "SSE",
                "ORG",
                67,
                70
            ],
            [
                "HNB",
                "ORG",
                106,
                109
            ],
            [
                "HNB",
                "ORG",
                150,
                153
            ],
            [
                "Swashakthi Savings",
                "PRODUCT",
                324,
                342
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "HNB FINANCE been immense strength our lives HNB FINANCE been our financial partner over years now . Therefore , we have been able business",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB FINANCE",
                "ORG",
                0,
                11
            ],
            [
                "HNB",
                "ORG",
                44,
                47
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Paragraph": "HNB FINANCE been immense strength our lives",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB FINANCE",
                "ORG",
                0,
                11
            ]
        ]
    }
]