[
    [
        "ACH",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "AG ZTB BC Mitte",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "AUD Canada Bank Montreal",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "Anagi ComBank range",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Australia",
        "GPE"
    ],
    [
        "BCITITMM Italy Banco",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "BIC Code Swift CCY Account",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Bank",
        "GPE"
    ],
    [
        "Business Loans",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "CAD China Standard Chartered Bank",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Cards ComBank Cards",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Cards Loans Savings",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Chung ku",
        "PERSON"
    ],
    [
        "Classic Debit Cards",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "ComBank",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "ComBank App",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "ComBank Apps",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "ComBank Best Bank Sri Lanka Global Finance",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "ComBank Cards",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "ComBank ComBank App",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "ComBank ComBank ComBank",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "ComBank Credit Card",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "ComBank Credit Cards",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "ComBank Credit Debit Cards",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "ComBank Debit Card",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "ComBank Digital",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "ComBank Digital ComBank Digital",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "ComBank Golds",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "ComBank Max Rewards",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "ComBank Max Rewards ComBank Digital",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "ComBank Personal Banking",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "ComBank Personal Loans",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "ComBank east Vavunathivu second",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Commercial Bank",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "Commercial Bank Ceylon",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "Commercial Bank Ceylon PLC",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "Commercial Bank Ceylon Vavunathivu Batticaloa",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "Commercial Bank Diribala Development Loan",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "Commercial House",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "Complaint Reporting Format",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Content Bigger Text Bigger Cursor Readable",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "Country Name Address Bank",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Credit Card",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Credit Cards",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Credit Debit Cards",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "DIFC",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "Debit Cards",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Digital Bank Account Flash Digital Bank Account Flash",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Digital Banking",
        "SERVICE"
    ],
    [
        "Discount Credit Debit",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Dubai Financial Services Authority",
        "SERVICE"
    ],
    [
        "Fixed Deposits",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Flash Digital Bank Account",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Flash Digital Bank Account Flash",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Flash Digital Bank Account Flash Digital Bank Account Flash",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Foreign Account Tax Compliance",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Foreign Account Tax Compliance Act FATCA",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Foreign Financial Institution",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "Germany",
        "GPE"
    ],
    [
        "Gold Loans",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Gold Silver Credit Cards",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Home Loans",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "IDIBINBB India Standard Chartered Bank Mumbai Crescenzo",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Indian Bank Corporate Office",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "Italy",
        "GPE"
    ],
    [
        "JPY Korea Korea Exchange Bank",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "Japan",
        "GPE"
    ],
    [
        "KG Rugby Team",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Korea Woori Bank",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "LankaPay Technnovation Awards",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Latest News ComBank",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Main Accounts",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Mainzer Landstrasse Frankfurt",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Milan",
        "GPE"
    ],
    [
        "Minor Youth Accounts",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "More",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "More Info",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "More Info Classic Debit Cards",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "More Info Easy Payment Great",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "More Info Upto Discount Credit Debit",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "More Info Visa Infinite Card",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Navigation Highlight Links Page",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "New Zealand Banking Group Limited",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "Personal Loans",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Piazza Della Scala",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Premium Credit Cards",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Prepaid Card Balance",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "R. Loan",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "RemitPlus RemitPlus",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "RemitPlus RemitPlus Safe",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "RemitPlus Safe",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Remittances Credit Card",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "SCBLINBB Italy",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "SME",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "Safe",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "Sanath Manatunge",
        "PERSON"
    ],
    [
        "Self Registration Portal",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Senior Citizens Accounts",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Senior Citizens Exclusive",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Services Savings Accounts",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Sri Lanka Commercial Bank Ceylon",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "Sri Lanka Global Finance",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "Sri Lankans Students",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "SriLankan Airlines",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Substantial Beneficial Owner",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Sumitomo Mitsui Banking Corporation International Business Operations Dept",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "Tokyo",
        "GPE"
    ],
    [
        "Tools Calculator Rewards Promotion",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "UNCRITMM Japan Standard",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Upto Discount Credit Debit",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "Visa Commercial Bank Ceylon",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "Visa Infinite Card",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "digital bank",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "ePassbook ePassbook ePassbook",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "online banking here",
        "SERVICE"
    ],
    [
        "selection Savings Accounts",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "today",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "tomorrow",
        "DATE"
    ]
]