[
    {
        "Sentence": "HNB FINANCE has been an immense strength to our lives HNB FINANCE has been our financial partner for over years now Therefore we have been able do business according to so enjoy the benefit of obtaining money for the business while saving As was able to get loan without any guarantors through Swashakthi Savings was able to easily get the money needed",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB FINANCE",
                "ORG",
                0,
                11
            ],
            [
                "HNB FINANCE",
                "ORG",
                54,
                65
            ],
            [
                "Swashakthi Savings",
                "PRODUCT",
                294,
                312
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Sentence": "HNB FINANCE clinches Bronze at TAGS Awards",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB FINANCE",
                "ORG",
                0,
                11
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Sentence": "HNB FINANCE appoints Anura Pathirage to Board of Directors HNB FINANCE PLC appoints Mr Rajive Dissanayake as Chairman HNB FINANCE clinches Bronze at TAGS Awards HNB FINANCE appoints Dr Prasad Samarasinghe to Board of Directors HNB FINANCE appoints Anura Pathirage to Board of Directors HNB FINANCE PLC appoints Mr Rajive Dissanayake as Chairman HNB FINANCE clinches Bronze at TAGS Awards HNB FINANCE appoints Dr Prasad Samarasinghe to Board of Directors HNB FINANCE appoints Anura Pathirage to Board of Directors HNB FINANCE PLC appoints Mr Rajive Dissanayake as Chairman prev next",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB FINANCE",
                "ORG",
                0,
                11
            ],
            [
                "Anura Pathirage to Board",
                "ORG",
                21,
                45
            ],
            [
                "HNB FINANCE PLC",
                "ORG",
                59,
                74
            ],
            [
                "Rajive Dissanayake",
                "PERSON",
                87,
                105
            ],
            [
                "HNB",
                "ORG",
                118,
                121
            ],
            [
                "TAGS Awards",
                "PRODUCT",
                149,
                160
            ],
            [
                "Samarasinghe to Board",
                "ORG",
                192,
                213
            ],
            [
                "Anura Pathirage to Board",
                "ORG",
                248,
                272
            ],
            [
                "HNB FINANCE PLC",
                "ORG",
                286,
                301
            ],
            [
                "Rajive Dissanayake",
                "PERSON",
                314,
                332
            ],
            [
                "HNB",
                "ORG",
                345,
                348
            ],
            [
                "TAGS Awards",
                "PRODUCT",
                376,
                387
            ],
            [
                "Samarasinghe to Board",
                "ORG",
                419,
                440
            ],
            [
                "Anura Pathirage to Board",
                "ORG",
                475,
                499
            ],
            [
                "HNB FINANCE PLC",
                "ORG",
                513,
                528
            ],
            [
                "Rajive Dissanayake",
                "PERSON",
                541,
                559
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Sentence": "Services That Offer You Convenience and Flexibility",
        "entities": []
    },
    {
        "Sentence": "Success Stories Our keen focus on entrepreneurs across the country enables us to boost SME SSE communities to reach their full potential",
        "entities": [
            [
                "SME",
                "ORG",
                87,
                90
            ],
            [
                "SSE",
                "ORG",
                91,
                94
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Sentence": "News Updates Read our latest news and updates HNB FINANCE appoints Anura Pathirage to Board of Directors HNB FINANCE PLC appoints Mr Rajive Dissanayake as Chairman HNB FINANCE clinches Bronze at TAGS Awards HNB FINANCE appoints Dr Prasad Samarasinghe to Board of Directors HNB FINANCE appoints Anura Pathirage to Board of Directors HNB FINANCE PLC appoints Mr Rajive Dissanayake as Chairman HNB FINANCE clinches Bronze at TAGS Awards HNB FINANCE appoints Dr Prasad Samarasinghe to Board of Directors HNB FINANCE appoints Anura Pathirage to Board of Directors HNB FINANCE PLC appoints Mr Rajive Dissanayake as Chairman prev next",
        "entities": [
            [
                "News Updates Read",
                "PRODUCT",
                0,
                17
            ],
            [
                "HNB",
                "ORG",
                46,
                49
            ],
            [
                "Anura Pathirage to Board",
                "ORG",
                67,
                91
            ],
            [
                "HNB FINANCE PLC",
                "ORG",
                105,
                120
            ],
            [
                "Rajive Dissanayake",
                "PERSON",
                133,
                151
            ],
            [
                "HNB",
                "ORG",
                164,
                167
            ],
            [
                "TAGS Awards",
                "PRODUCT",
                195,
                206
            ],
            [
                "Samarasinghe to Board",
                "ORG",
                238,
                259
            ],
            [
                "Anura Pathirage to Board",
                "ORG",
                294,
                318
            ],
            [
                "HNB FINANCE PLC",
                "ORG",
                332,
                347
            ],
            [
                "Rajive Dissanayake",
                "PERSON",
                360,
                378
            ],
            [
                "HNB",
                "ORG",
                391,
                394
            ],
            [
                "TAGS Awards",
                "PRODUCT",
                422,
                433
            ],
            [
                "Samarasinghe to Board",
                "ORG",
                465,
                486
            ],
            [
                "Anura Pathirage to Board",
                "ORG",
                521,
                545
            ],
            [
                "HNB FINANCE PLC",
                "ORG",
                559,
                574
            ],
            [
                "Rajive Dissanayake",
                "PERSON",
                587,
                605
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Sentence": "HNB FINANCE appoints Dr Prasad Samarasinghe to Board of Directors",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB FINANCE",
                "ORG",
                0,
                11
            ],
            [
                "Samarasinghe to Board",
                "ORG",
                31,
                52
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Sentence": "Success Stories Our keen focus on entrepreneurs across the country enables us to boost SME SSE communities to reach their full potential HNB FINANCE has been an immense strength to our lives HNB FINANCE has been our financial partner for over years now Therefore we have been able do business according to so enjoy the benefit of obtaining money for the business while saving As was able to get loan without any guarantors through Swashakthi Savings was able to easily get the money needed",
        "entities": [
            [
                "SME",
                "ORG",
                87,
                90
            ],
            [
                "SSE",
                "ORG",
                91,
                94
            ],
            [
                "HNB FINANCE",
                "ORG",
                137,
                148
            ],
            [
                "HNB FINANCE",
                "ORG",
                191,
                202
            ],
            [
                "Swashakthi Savings",
                "PRODUCT",
                431,
                449
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Sentence": "HNB FINANCE has been an immense strength to our lives HNB FINANCE has been our financial partner for over years now Therefore we have been able do business according to so",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB FINANCE",
                "ORG",
                0,
                11
            ],
            [
                "HNB FINANCE",
                "ORG",
                54,
                65
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Sentence": "HNB FINANCE appoints Anura Pathirage to Board of Directors HNB FINANCE PLC appoints Mr Rajive Dissanayake as Chairman HNB FINANCE clinches Bronze at TAGS Awards HNB FINANCE appoints Dr Prasad Samarasinghe to Board of Directors HNB FINANCE appoints Anura Pathirage to Board of Directors HNB FINANCE PLC appoints Mr Rajive Dissanayake as Chairman HNB FINANCE clinches Bronze at TAGS Awards HNB FINANCE appoints Dr Prasad Samarasinghe to Board of Directors HNB FINANCE appoints Anura Pathirage to Board of Directors HNB FINANCE PLC appoints Mr Rajive Dissanayake as Chairman",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB FINANCE",
                "ORG",
                0,
                11
            ],
            [
                "Anura Pathirage to Board",
                "ORG",
                21,
                45
            ],
            [
                "HNB FINANCE PLC",
                "ORG",
                59,
                74
            ],
            [
                "Rajive Dissanayake",
                "PERSON",
                87,
                105
            ],
            [
                "HNB",
                "ORG",
                118,
                121
            ],
            [
                "TAGS Awards",
                "PRODUCT",
                149,
                160
            ],
            [
                "Samarasinghe to Board",
                "ORG",
                192,
                213
            ],
            [
                "Anura Pathirage to Board",
                "ORG",
                248,
                272
            ],
            [
                "HNB FINANCE PLC",
                "ORG",
                286,
                301
            ],
            [
                "Rajive Dissanayake",
                "PERSON",
                314,
                332
            ],
            [
                "HNB",
                "ORG",
                345,
                348
            ],
            [
                "TAGS Awards",
                "PRODUCT",
                376,
                387
            ],
            [
                "Samarasinghe to Board",
                "ORG",
                419,
                440
            ],
            [
                "Anura Pathirage to Board",
                "ORG",
                475,
                499
            ],
            [
                "HNB FINANCE PLC",
                "ORG",
                513,
                528
            ],
            [
                "Rajive Dissanayake",
                "PERSON",
                541,
                559
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Sentence": "Products to Help You Grow",
        "entities": []
    },
    {
        "Sentence": "Sri Lanka leading integrated financial service provider HNB Finance established water purification system and renovated the Mohoththuwarama Pri",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Sri Lanka",
                "GPE",
                0,
                9
            ],
            [
                "HNB Finance",
                "ORG",
                56,
                67
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Sentence": "HNB Finance is subsidiary of Hatton National Bank PLC and continues to operate with an unblemished record of almost two decades as leader in the finance industry with diverse portfolio of financial products and services",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB Finance",
                "ORG",
                0,
                11
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Sentence": "HNB FINANCE PLC appoints Mr Rajive Dissanayake as Chairman",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB FINANCE PLC",
                "ORG",
                0,
                15
            ],
            [
                "Rajive Dissanayake",
                "PERSON",
                28,
                46
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Sentence": "HNB FINANCE has been an immense strength to our lives",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB FINANCE",
                "ORG",
                0,
                11
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Sentence": "Services That Offer You Convenience and Flexibility HNB Finance PLC Strength Born of Strength HNB Finance is subsidiary of Hatton National Bank PLC and continues to operate with an unblemished record of almost two decades as leader in the finance industry with diverse portfolio of financial products and services Products to Help You Grow Shaping your future with products that encourage growth Success Stories Our keen focus on entrepreneurs across the country enables us to boost SME SSE communities to reach their full potential HNB FINANCE has been an immense strength to our lives HNB FINANCE has been our financial partner for over years now Therefore we have been able do business according to so enjoy the benefit of obtaining money for the business while saving As was able to get loan without any guarantors through Swashakthi Savings was able to easily get the money needed About Us pioneering financial institution fuelled by passionate team that aims to provide customer centric well diversified products and services in responsible and sustainable way Customers Employees Branches Mehewara CSR Projects The Mehewara fund is series of ongoing CSR projects that helps our customers in need The fund is maintained with the financial contribution of our dedicated employees and the organisation HNB Finance creates an oasis in Mohoththuwarama Primary School Sri Lanka leading integrated financial service provider HNB Finance established water purification system and renovated the Mohoththuwarama Pri News Updates Read our latest news and updates HNB FINANCE appoints Anura Pathirage to Board of Directors HNB FINANCE PLC appoints Mr Rajive Dissanayake as Chairman HNB FINANCE clinches Bronze at TAGS Awards HNB FINANCE appoints Dr Prasad Samarasinghe to Board of Directors HNB FINANCE appoints Anura Pathirage to Board of Directors HNB FINANCE PLC appoints Mr Rajive Dissanayake as Chairman HNB FINANCE clinches Bronze at TAGS Awards HNB FINANCE appoints Dr Prasad Samarasinghe to Board of Directors HNB FINANCE appoints Anura Pathirage to Board of Directors HNB FINANCE PLC appoints Mr Rajive Dissanayake as Chairman prev next Great Place To Work Certified TAGS Awards",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB Finance PLC",
                "ORG",
                52,
                67
            ],
            [
                "SME",
                "ORG",
                483,
                486
            ],
            [
                "SSE",
                "ORG",
                487,
                490
            ],
            [
                "HNB FINANCE",
                "ORG",
                533,
                544
            ],
            [
                "HNB FINANCE",
                "ORG",
                587,
                598
            ],
            [
                "Swashakthi Savings",
                "PRODUCT",
                827,
                845
            ],
            [
                "HNB Finance",
                "ORG",
                1425,
                1436
            ],
            [
                "HNB",
                "ORG",
                1559,
                1562
            ],
            [
                "Anura Pathirage to Board",
                "ORG",
                1580,
                1604
            ],
            [
                "HNB FINANCE PLC",
                "ORG",
                1618,
                1633
            ],
            [
                "Rajive Dissanayake",
                "PERSON",
                1646,
                1664
            ],
            [
                "HNB",
                "ORG",
                1677,
                1680
            ],
            [
                "TAGS Awards",
                "PRODUCT",
                1708,
                1719
            ],
            [
                "Samarasinghe to Board",
                "ORG",
                1751,
                1772
            ],
            [
                "Anura Pathirage to Board",
                "ORG",
                1807,
                1831
            ],
            [
                "HNB FINANCE PLC",
                "ORG",
                1845,
                1860
            ],
            [
                "Rajive Dissanayake",
                "PERSON",
                1873,
                1891
            ],
            [
                "HNB",
                "ORG",
                1904,
                1907
            ],
            [
                "TAGS Awards",
                "PRODUCT",
                1935,
                1946
            ],
            [
                "Samarasinghe to Board",
                "ORG",
                1978,
                1999
            ],
            [
                "Anura Pathirage to Board",
                "ORG",
                2034,
                2058
            ],
            [
                "HNB FINANCE PLC",
                "ORG",
                2072,
                2087
            ],
            [
                "Rajive Dissanayake",
                "PERSON",
                2100,
                2118
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Sentence": "Products to Help You Grow Shaping your future with products that encourage growth",
        "entities": []
    },
    {
        "Sentence": "HNB FINANCE has been our financial partner for over years now Therefore we have been able do business according to so",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB FINANCE",
                "ORG",
                0,
                11
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Sentence": "HNB FINANCE appoints Anura Pathirage to Board of Directors",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB FINANCE",
                "ORG",
                0,
                11
            ],
            [
                "Anura Pathirage to Board of Directors",
                "ORG",
                21,
                58
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Sentence": "enjoy the benefit of obtaining money for the business while saving As was able to get loan without any guarantors through Swashakthi Savings was able to easily get the money needed",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Swashakthi Savings",
                "PRODUCT",
                122,
                140
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Sentence": "Shaping your future with products that encourage growth",
        "entities": []
    },
    {
        "Sentence": "Our keen focus on entrepreneurs across the country enables us to boost SME SSE communities to reach their full potential",
        "entities": [
            [
                "SME",
                "ORG",
                71,
                74
            ],
            [
                "SSE",
                "ORG",
                75,
                78
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Sentence": "HNB Finance creates an oasis in Mohoththuwarama Primary School",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB Finance",
                "ORG",
                0,
                11
            ],
            [
                "Mohoththuwarama Primary School",
                "PRODUCT",
                32,
                62
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Sentence": "HNB Finance creates an oasis in Mohoththuwarama Primary School Sri Lanka leading integrated financial service provider HNB Finance established water purification system and renovated the Mohoththuwarama Pri",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB Finance",
                "ORG",
                0,
                11
            ],
            [
                "HNB Finance",
                "ORG",
                119,
                130
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Sentence": "HNB Finance PLC Strength Born of Strength HNB Finance is subsidiary of Hatton National Bank PLC and continues to operate with an unblemished record of almost two decades as leader in the finance industry with diverse portfolio of financial products and services",
        "entities": [
            [
                "HNB Finance PLC",
                "ORG",
                0,
                15
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Sentence": "Mehewara CSR Projects The Mehewara fund is series of ongoing CSR projects that helps our customers in need The fund is maintained with the financial contribution of our dedicated employees and the organisation HNB Finance creates an oasis in Mohoththuwarama Primary School Sri Lanka leading integrated financial service provider HNB Finance established water purification system and renovated the Mohoththuwarama Pri",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Mehewara CSR Projects",
                "SERVICE",
                0,
                21
            ],
            [
                "HNB Finance",
                "ORG",
                329,
                340
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Sentence": "pioneering financial institution fuelled by passionate team that aims to provide customer centric well diversified products and services in responsible and sustainable way",
        "entities": []
    },
    {
        "Sentence": "Read our latest news and updates",
        "entities": []
    },
    {
        "Sentence": "Mehewara CSR Projects The Mehewara fund is series of ongoing CSR projects that helps our customers in need The fund is maintained with the financial contribution of our dedicated employees and the organisation",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Mehewara CSR Projects",
                "SERVICE",
                0,
                21
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Sentence": "As was able to get loan without any guarantors through Swashakthi Savings was able to easily get the money needed",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Swashakthi Savings",
                "PRODUCT",
                55,
                73
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Sentence": "About Us pioneering financial institution fuelled by passionate team that aims to provide customer centric well diversified products and services in responsible and sustainable way Customers Employees Branches",
        "entities": []
    },
    {
        "Sentence": "News Updates Read our latest news and updates",
        "entities": [
            [
                "News Updates Read",
                "PRODUCT",
                0,
                17
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Sentence": "The Mehewara fund is series of ongoing CSR projects that helps our customers in need The fund is maintained with the financial contribution of our dedicated employees and the organisation",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Mehewara",
                "ORG",
                4,
                12
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "Sentence": "Great Place To Work Certified TAGS Awards",
        "entities": []
    },
    {
        "Sentence": "About Us pioneering financial institution fuelled by passionate team that aims to provide customer centric well diversified products and services in responsible and sustainable way",
        "entities": []
    },
    {
        "Sentence": "enjoy the benefit of obtaining money for the business while saving",
        "entities": []
    },
    {
        "Sentence": "Great Place To Work Certified",
        "entities": []
    }
]